Multiple use of heart and great vessels reveal normal intracardic and great vessel relationships.
Cardiac function is normal.
There is no significant chamber, enlargement or hypertrophy.
There is no pre-cardial effusion or visitation seen.
Doppler interrogation including colour flow imaging reveals systemic venous return to
the written right atom with normal tricuspid inflow.
Pulmonary outflow is normal at the wall.
Pulmonary venous return is to the left atom.
The left arterial spectrum is intact.
Material inflow and ascending autra flow are normal.
The aortic valve is tri-lifted.
The coronary arteries appear to be normal in their origins.
The aortic arch is left-sided and patent with normal descending autra pulsatility.